kerala365.com 2018-04-12

# Privacy Policy - kerala365.com

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you  subscribe to our newsletter or making a comment.

When you making a comment on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address , we will collect your  IP address during that process. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google\’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to the users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.[visit advertising opt-out page here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Do we use cookies?**

No, we do not use cookies, .  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google\’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to the users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.[visit advertising opt-out page here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on August 11, 2010

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.kerala365.com  
Kollam, Kerala  
India  
info.kerala365 (at) gmail.com
